<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ouisync</title>
    <link>https://ouisync.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ouisync</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Everything is mine</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:52 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ouisync.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:41:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/security/</guid>
      <description>Encryption in a distributed file sharing system Ouisync offers users a secure way to share and synchronize data across devices. Due to the distributed (peer-to-peer) nature of Ouisync, where concurrent changes to files and directories are possible, the directory structure of Ouisync is quite elaborate. Whenever two or more users modify a file in a directory concurrently, Ouisync’s architecture guarantees that no information is lost. Moreover, Ouisync also protects the content (files and repositories) and the structure of your file systems by implementing end-to-end encryption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 13:32:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/community/</guid>
      <description>Get in Touch! For support questions, press and media, and feedback, you can contact the Ouisync team at: support [at] ouisync [dot] net.
 View the Source Code  If you are interested in Ouisync&amp;#39;s source code please check the following Git repositories:
Ouisync App
  Ouisync Flutter Plugin
  Ouisync CLI
  Ouisync Library
    Contact Us  To contact the Ouisync team, send an email to support [at] ouisync [dot] net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:14:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/support/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions  Getting Started    What is a repository?  A repository is simply a place where you can store and share your files and folders securely, using Ouisync. You can think of it as a root folder, or even a safe, that will contain other folders and files that you want to share with your peers.
   Where can I see my repositories  When you open the Ouisync app, after the onboarding screens you will see the main screen listing all the repositories you have created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello News</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/news/hello-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/news/hello-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Blog</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/blog/hello-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/blog/hello-blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:57:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/about/</guid>
      <description>About Ouisync Ouisync is a private and resilient solution for syncing files and folders with your devices, contacts and groups.
Easy to use  Simply install and quickly create files and folders to sync and share with trusted devices, contacts and/or groups.
 Offline-first  Ouisync uses an innovative, synchronous, peer-to-peer design that allows users to access and share files and folders whether or not your device can connect to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ouisync Terms of Use &amp; Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://ouisync.net/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:57:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouisync.net/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Ouisync Terms of Use &amp;amp; Privacy Notice 1. Overview This Ouisync Terms of Use (the “Agreement”), along with our Privacy Notice (collectively, the “Terms”), govern your use of Ouisync - an online file synchronization protocol and software. By installing and running the Ouisync application, you indicate your assent to be bound by and to comply with this Agreement between you and eQualitie inc. (“eQualitie”, “we”, or “us”). Usage of the Ouisync application and the Ouisync network (the Service) is provided by eQualitie at no cost and is intended for use as is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
