<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ouisync</title>
    <link>https://willow446.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ouisync</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Everything is mine</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:52 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://willow446.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:41:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/security/</guid>
      <description>Security </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:10:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/download/</guid>
      <description>Download Ouisync Freely backup and share files using peer-to-peer networking.
  Android   Signature         Windows  Signature        Linux  Signature       🚧 iOS (Coming Soon!)  Signature     Download Ouisync Server Docker Container  For self-hosting a Ouisync server.
Ouisync Server   Verify APK for Android  Run this to verify that the APK has a valid signature from the certificate with the fingerprint shown below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 13:32:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/community/</guid>
      <description>Get Involved! We&amp;rsquo;d love your support in making Ouisync as useful and accessible as possible. Ouisync is a completely Free/Libre/Open Source project, and there are many ways to contribute!
View the Source Code  If you are interested in Ouisync&#39;s source code please check the following Git repositories:
Ouisync App
  Ouisync Flutter Plugin
  Ouisync CLI
  Ouisync Library
  Read the Whitepaper   Get in Touch  To contact the Ouisync team, send an email to support [at] ouisync [dot] net.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:14:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Frequently Asked Questions Getting Started   What is a repository?  A repository is simply a place where you can store and share your files and folders securely, using Ouisync. You can think of it as a root folder, or even a safe, that will contain other folders and files that you want to share with your peers.
   Where can I see my repositories?  When you open the Ouisync app, after the onboarding screens you will see the main screen listing all the repositories you have created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello News</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/news/hello-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/news/hello-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Blog</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/blog/hello-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:22:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/blog/hello-blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:57:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About
About Ouisync Ouisync is a private and resilient solution for syncing files and folders with your devices, contacts and groups.
Features Easy to use  Simply install and quickly create files and folders to sync and share with trusted devices, contacts and/or groups.
 Offline-first  Ouisync uses an innovative, synchronous, peer-to-peer design that allows users to access and share files and folders whether or not your device can connect to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ouisync Terms of Use &amp; Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://willow446.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 23:57:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://willow446.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Ouisync Terms of Use &amp;amp; Privacy Notice 1. Overview This Ouisync Terms of Use (the “Agreement”), along with our Privacy Notice (collectively, the “Terms”), govern your use of Ouisync - an online file synchronization protocol and software. By installing and running the Ouisync application, you indicate your assent to be bound by and to comply with this Agreement between you and eQualitie inc. (“eQualitie”, “we”, or “us”). Usage of the Ouisync application and the Ouisync network (the Service) is provided by eQualitie at no cost and is intended for use as is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
